development: &non_production_settings
  api_key: 8u5ixtdnq9csc84cok0owswgo         # grab one from http://textcaptcha.com/api
  bcrypt_salt: $2a$10$j0bmycH.SVfD1b5mpEGPpe # must be a valid bcrypt salt, we've generated this one for you randomly
                                             # generate another with; require 'bcrypt'; BCrypt::Engine.generate_salt
  bcrypt_cost: 10 # optional (default is 10) must be > 4 (a larger number means slower encryption)
                  # see http://bcrypt-ruby.rubyforge.org for more information on bcrypt
  questions:
      - question: 'Is ice hot or cold?'
        answers: 'cold'
      - question: 'what color is an orange?'
        answers: 'orange'
      - question: 'what is two plus 3?'
        answers: '5,five'
      - question: 'what is 5 times two?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'How many colors in the list, green, brown, foot and blue?'
        answers: '3,three'
      - question: 'what is Georges name?'
        answers: 'george'
      - question: '11 minus 1?'
        answers: '10,ten'
      - question: 'is boiling water hot or cold?'
        answers: 'hot'
      - question: 'what color is my blue shirt today?'
        answers: 'blue'
      - question: 'what is 16 plus 4?'
        answers: '20,twenty'

test:
  *non_production_settings

production:
  *non_production_settings
